{
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionNumber": 1,
            "question": "Ile metrów wysokości ma wieża Eiffle?",
            "answers": {
                "a": 222,
                "b": 120,
                "c": 300,
                "d": 333
            },
            "goodAnswer": 300
        },
        {
            "questionNumber": 2,
            "question": "Jaki jest najcięższy ssak na świecie?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Płetwal Błekitny",
                "b": "Słoń",
                "c": "Nosorożec",
                "d": "Hipopotam"
            },
            "goodAnswer": "Płetwal Błekitny"
        },
                {
            "questionNumber": 3,
            "question": "Ile metrów wysokości ma wieża Eiffle?",
            "answers": {
                "a": 222,
                "b": 120,
                "c": 300,
                "d": 333
            },
            "goodAnswer": 300
        },
        {
            "questionNumber": 4,
            "question": "Jaki jest najcięższy ssak na świecie?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Płetwal Błekitny",
                "b": "Słoń",
                "c": "Nosorożec",
                "d": "Hipopotam"
            },
            "goodAnswer": "Płetwal Błekitny"
        },
		        {
            "questionNumber": 5,
            "question": "Ile metrów wysokości ma wieża Eiffle?",
            "answers": {
                "a": 222,
                "b": 120,
                "c": 300,
                "d": 333
            },
            "goodAnswer": 300
        },
        {
            "questionNumber": 6,
            "question": "Jaki jest najcięższy ssak na świecie?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Płetwal Błekitny",
                "b": "Słoń",
                "c": "Nosorożec",
                "d": "Hipopotam"
            },
            "goodAnswer": "Płetwal Błekitny"
        },
		        {
            "questionNumber": 7,
            "question": "Ile metrów wysokości ma wieża Eiffle?",
            "answers": {
                "a": 222,
                "b": 120,
                "c": 300,
                "d": 333
            },
            "goodAnswer": 300
        },
        {
            "questionNumber": 8,
            "question": "Jaki jest najcięższy ssak na świecie?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Płetwal Błekitny",
                "b": "Słoń",
                "c": "Nosorożec",
                "d": "Hipopotam"
            },
            "goodAnswer": "Płetwal Błekitny"
        },
		        {
            "questionNumber": 9,
            "question": "Ile metrów wysokości ma wieża Eiffle?",
            "answers": {
                "a": 222,
                "b": 120,
                "c": 300,
                "d": 333
            },
            "goodAnswer": 300
        },
        {
            "questionNumber": 10,
            "question": "Jaki jest najcięższy ssak na świecie?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Płetwal Błekitny",
                "b": "Słoń",
                "c": "Nosorożec",
                "d": "Hipopotam"
            },
            "goodAnswer": "Płetwal Błekitny"
        }
    ]
}